Toothpaste is making you dumber.
Let me explain.
The majority of all toothpaste
have a toxic chemical in them
that destroys an important gland in your brain.
This substance is known as fluoride.
The government wants you to think that
fluoride is good for you
and that it's safe,
but that's just a lie.
Fluoride calcifies an important gland in your brain
known as the pineal gland.
This gland is responsible for many things
like your circadian cycle and hormone secretion.
Many also believe that the pineal gland is
the seed of the soul
and is where you unlock higher consciousness.
Side effects of having a calcified pineal gland
include a wide range of neuronal diseases
like alzheimer's
and also disruption of melatonin and serotonin levels.
To combat this,
you have two options.
Find a trusted brand of fluoride free toothpaste
or make your own toothpaste by mixing coconut oil,
baking soda,
sea salt, and essential oils like mint.
If they can't get you with toothpaste,
they'll try and get you with the tap water.
There's a reason
fluoride is banned in many European countries.
The United States has
one of the most corrupt systems in the world,
all to keep you sick and dumb. Luckily,
there are people trying to expose this corruption,
like me. It's up to you to decide what you wanna believe.
The lies or the real truth.
Follow Divine Herbal roots
for more daily tips about real health.